Melancholy is a new derivative in the rival of KineticPlasma Fonts' Asimov, which is a derivative of Roboto.

Reupload note:
FontSpace just got the rid of Gnuolane derivation, due to copyright issues witn Typodermic Fonts, Inc. So, I uploaded a new Robot clone for you.

Modifications:
New capital letter R, new lowecase letter l, new straight quotes(an apostrophe and a straight quotation mark), new dollar sign and new number 1.
The different superscipt 1 and fractions 1/2 and 1/4.
The capital I has now contained serifs.

About this font:
Melancholy was named after the Touhou Project character, Medicine Melancholy, a doll yōkai that lives on Nameless Hill surrounded by poisonous suzuran (lily of the valley) flowers.

Disclaimer:
Heaven Castro has NOT been affiliated with Google Web Designs(United States) and Team Shanghai Alice(Japan, formley ZUN Soft).
Team Shanghai Alice is best known for the Touhou Project game, Phantasmagoria of Flower View.
Don't ask me with this derivative! This is the derivative font I've ever been made! I'll be back!